SHAHZHOB AHMED KHAN

Phone:

0345-316-1994

Email: shazzahmed57@gmail.com

LinkedIn: GitHub:

 $\underline{https://www.linkedin.com/in/shahzhob-ahmed-khan/}$

https://github.com/SHAZZ57

OBJECTIVE:

I am full-stack developer with over 3+ years of industry experience in application design, development and maintenance using Microsoft .NET technologies. Strong knowledge of .NET platform with an in depth knowledge of Object-oriented design, SOLID design principles.

Over the past few years, I have been developing using C#, ASP.NET MVC/ ASP.NET Core / ASP.NET REST-based Web APIs and various front-end libraries/frameworks (e.g., jQuery,

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:

AngularJS/ IONIC/Angular2+ etc.).

ITSOLUTION24x7

Full Stack Developer | OCT 2019 - Present

- Banking Application Development using C#, ASP.Net MVC and MVVM, ASP.Net REST APIs, SOAP APIs, Entity Framework, Code First and Model First approaches, Repository Pattern.
- Front-end development using Angular, Razor views, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQurey, AJAX.
- > Windows services development.
- Database management using MySQL, SQL Server.
- Develop Time logging Desktop on .Net
- Develop ERP

BITSOLUTION

SOFTWARE ENGINEER | OCT 2017 - SEP 2019

➤ Involved in database design of project, back end coding, logic making migrations through entity framework etc.

ARCUBE DIGITAL

JR DEVELOPER /DESIGNER| JULY 2016 - MAY 2017

➤ Involve in research and development (R&D) of company's existing and new projects challenges.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND:

- ➤ HAMDARD UNIVERSITY

 MS SOFTWARE ENGNEERING | 2019- Cont...
- > IQRA UNIVERSITY

Bachelor in Computer Science | 2018

- ➤ GOVT. CITY COLLEGE
 Intermediate (Pre-engineering) | 2011
- ➤ LONDON CAMBRIDGE SCHOOL Matric (Computer Science) | 2009

TECH SKILLS:

- HTML5/CSS3
- JavaScript
- C#/Asp.NET
- REST WEB API
- Angular

- Bootstrap
- ASP.NET MVC
- SQL/NoSQL
- Entity Framework
- JQuery

TECHNOLOGIES:

- Node JS
- React JS
- WordPress
- Firebase
- Git
- Linux/Windows
- MS SQL Server/MySQL
- Express.js
- Entity Framework
- IONIC
- JSON
- Ajax
- Jenkins
- React.js
- React Native

PROJECTS:

Name: Winner Winner

Technologies:.NET Core, NodeJS, PostgresQL,

React/ React Native

Description: Winner Winner is Claw Gaming App which is used to play claw game virtually and shipped Prize through Amazon, Alibaba and other channel, it has dashboard on React JS, Front End App on React Native and Backend consisted on Node JS and .NET Core.

Name: TIME LOGGER

Technologies: ASP .NET MVC, MS SQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Entity Framework

Description: A brief WEB APP based and WPF on .Net technologies. Where different panels were created i.e. Admin, Client and Worker. Where we can track employees Working Their Screen Shots Reports, Projects working on through Admin can perform multiple task like accepting new registrations, posting & deleting add timing.

ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS:

Internet Searching New Technologies

Automobile Cars in general, sports cars, Cricket

Traveling France, Malaysia, Belgium, Italy, Japan

CERTIFICATIONS:

APTECH COMPUTER EDUCATION

Aptech Certified Computer Professional (PRO) | 2013-2016

LANGUAGES:

Urdu, English.

Name: SMART PRO MAN (Mobile APP)

Technologies: Ionic/Angular, CSS, LARAVEL

Description: A interactive app for TECHNICIANS

and CLIENT.

Where client can make a complaint and technician accept it and whole quotation are save and whole admin panel

Role based.

Name: Dale! (Banking WEB APP Columbian based)

Technologies: ASP .NET MVC, Angular, MS SQL, HTML,

CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Entity Framework, Radis

Description: A Banking APP where Admin panel is based on MVC WEB APP and Client Side Build on

ANGULAR.

Name: ERP COTTON LINT

Technologies: C#, Win Forms, MS SQL, Crystal Reports **Description:** A desktop application where user can Weight their product and it will be managing by admin panel and Reports can be view and CRUD OPERATION an order or modify it and will get an instant printable slip. Relational DB was created to store all the transactions and to generate custom reports as per business needs.